Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series II. Dean's Files
  - B. Francille Firebaugh (1988-1999)
    - 2) Speeches and Trip Reports
      - b)Trip Reports
        - Tompkins County Cooperative Extension Association Annual Meeting, 1991-11-21 (Box 30, Folder 65)
        - Travel Vouchers, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - Cornell Conference; Education of a Higher Order, 1992-01-06-1992-01-10 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - New York City and Houston, 1992-01-22-1992-01-26 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - Sage Chapel (PCM), 1992-03-01 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Florida Fund Raising; Travel Vouchers, 1992-03-02-1992-03-08 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - Hawaii and Malaysia; University Pertanium, 1992-03-31-1992-04-18 (Box 31, Folder 6-8)
        - Advisory Council, 1992-04-30-1992-05-01 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - NY State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1992-05-04 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - UAB Dinner; Comments about College, 1992-05-17 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - Empowerment Conference (Welcome), 1992-05-28 (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - AHEA Denver, Colorado, 1992-06-27-1992-07-01 (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Cooperative Extension; New York City, 1992-08-22 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Orientation; Fall, 1992-08-22 (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - Founders Dinner, 1992-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - Mr. and Mrs. George Cornell Visit, 1992-09-03 (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - Binghamton University Reception and Dinner, 1992-10-05 (Box 31, Folder 18)
        - Meeting with President Rhodes and Provost Nesheim, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - Extension Association Directors Dinner; College Update, 1992-10-21 (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - Orlando; The 1992 Family System, 1992-11-05-1992-11-06 (Box 31, Folder 21)
        - Leadership Tompkins, 1992-11-12 (Box 31, Folder 22)
        - New Faculty and Staff Dinner at the Parkway, 1992-12-04 (Box 31, Folder 23)
        - Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca; Founders Day, 1993-01-16 (Box 31, Folder 24)
        - Columbus, Phoenix, and Albuquerque, 1993-02-23-1993-03-02 (Box 31, Folder 25)
        - Tulsa and Dallas, 1993-03-26-1993-03-31 (Box 31, Folder 26)
        - University of Illinois; Paul A. Funk Recognition Awards Program, 1993-03-30 (Box 31, Folder 27)
        - Southern California, 1992-04-13-1992-04-18 (Box 31, Folder 28-29)
        - Alumnae Networking Brunch; Nancy Mills; Los Angles California, 1993-04-17 (Box 31, Folder 30)
        - Washington DC and New York City Trip, 1993-05-18-1993-05-23 (Box 31, Folder 31)
        - Retreat-Strategic Planning, 1992-06-01-1992-06-02 (Box 31, Folder 32)
        - AHEA-Orlando, Florida, 1993-06-26-1993-06-30 (Box 31, Folder 33)
        - Metropolitan Program; Ithaca, 1992-07-12 (Box 31, Folder 34)
        - Seattle, Washington Alumni Visits, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 35)
        - Family Advocacy Prevention Workshop- Welcome, 1993-09-13 (Box 31, Folder 36)
        - Buffalo SUNY Retreat, 1993-10-03-1993-10-05 (Box 31, Folder 37)
        - Cooperative Extension Jefferson County Annual Meeting, 1993-10-23 (Box 31, Folder 38-39)
        - NASULGC, Washington DC, 1993-11-10-1993-11-14 (Box 31, Folder 40)
        - Cornell in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1993-11-18-1993-11-21 (Box 31, Folder 41)
        - Ohio Alumni Trip, 1993-12-12-1993-12-15 (Box 31, Folder 42)
        - Florida Trip, 1994-01-08 (Box 31, Folder 43)
        - San Francisco, California Alumni- "After Cornell - Then What?", 1994-03 (Box 31, Folder 44)
        - California and Hong Kong, 1994-03 (Box 31, Folder 45-47)
        - Albany, New York, 1994-03-10 (Box 31, Folder 48)
        - Society for Human Ecology (SHE)- 7th conference- Michigan, 1994-04-21-1994-04-24 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
        - URIE Reception- Press Club- Washington DC, 1994-04-27 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Zamorano Board Meeting- Washington DC, 1994-05-12-1994-05-15 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Albany and New York City, 1994-05-17-1994-05-18 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Reunion, 1994-06-09-1994-06-11 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - AHEA- San Diego, 1994-06-18-1994-06-20 (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - North Carolina and Tennessee, 1994-07-26-1994-08-04 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
        - UN International Year of the Family Workshops, Asheville, North Carolina, 1994-07-29-1994-08-01 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Strategic Planning, 1994-09-08 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - New York City, 1994-10-01-1994-10-07 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - New York Department of Social Services, 1994-10-18 (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Guatemala, Zamorano, 1994-11-02-1994-11-06 (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1994-11-10-1994-11-12 (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1994-11-20 (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - Florida, 1994-12-01-1994-12-04 (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Holidays, 1994-12-16-1994-12-20 (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - New York City and Washington DC, 1995-01-24-1995-01-29 (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - New Faculty and Visiting Scholars; Dinner at the Dean's House, 1995-02-04-1995-02-05 (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Rochester, New York, 1995-03-31-1995-04-01 (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - Arkansas and New York Advisory Council Meeting, 1995-04-07-1995-04-10 (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - Washington DC, 1995-04-17-1995-04-18 (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - New York City Tower Club, 1995-05-18-1995-05-19 (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - Albany, 1995-06-02 (Box 32, Folder 27)
        - Zamorano Board Meeting, 1995-06-14-1995-06-18 (Box 32, Folder 28)
        - NASULGC- Washington DC, 1995-06-20-1995-06-21 (Box 32, Folder 29)
        - AHEA- New Orleans, 1995-07-24-1995-07-28 (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - Albany, 1995-07-18 (Box 32, Folder 31)
        - President Rawlings Tour of College of Human Ecology, 1995-07-21 (Box 32, Folder 32)
        - San Diego, California, 1995-08-03-1995-08-09 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - Penn State visit, 1995-08-23-1995-08-24 (Box 32, Folder 34)
        - Mary, Gale, and Joan visit to Cornell- President Rawlings, 1995-08-25 (Box 32, Folder 35)
        - New York City, 1995-09-13-1995-09-15 (Box 32, Folder 36)
        - Albany, 1995-10-05 (Box 32, Folder 37)
        - Statutory Open House-Welcome-Bailey Hall, 1995-10-21 (Box 32, Folder 38)
        - Albany, New York- Hank Dullea (Natoli Visit), 1995 (Box 32, Folder 39)
        - Meining Symposium, 1995-10-27 (Box 32, Folder 40)
        - Washington DC, 1995-10-31-1995-11-01 (Box 32, Folder 41)
        - Zamorano Board Meeting- Honduras, 1995-11-02-1995-11-06 (Box 32, Folder 42)
        - SUNY Chancellor's Forum-Bolton Landing, New York, 1995-11-12-1995-11-15 (Box 32, Folder 43)
        - New York City-EPE Advisory Council, 1995-11-15 (Box 32, Folder 44)
        - New Faculty and Promotion Dinner-Dean's House, 1995-11-18 (Box 32, Folder 45)
        - Holiday Cards, 1995-12 (Box 32, Folder 46)
        - Lunch with Martha Ohaus-New Jersey, 1995-12-06 (Box 32, Folder 47)
        - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1995-12-08 (Box 32, Folder 48)
        - New York City Families and Work Institute, 1995-12-14 (Box 32, Folder 49)
        - Visiting scholars dinner, 1996-09-09 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - Sabbatical luncheon, 1996-10-08 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - President's Council catering, 1996-10-08 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - New faculty/staff dinner, 1996-11-03 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - Chili dinner, 1997-02-13 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Breast cancer luncheon, 1997-05-07 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - Chairs' and Deans' Dinner, 1997-06-17 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - Transfers chili dinner, 1997-09-03 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - Dinner at 110 the Parkway, 1997-09-14 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - Dinner at 110 for Burkhauser's second visit, 1997-09-22 (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - Sabbatical luncheon, 1997-10-15 (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - Reception Policy Analysis and Management graduates (Burkhauser), dinner (Steidl, Rakow, etc.), 1997-11-21-1997-11-23 (Box 61, Folder 12)
        - Olsen dinner; 110 The Parkway, 1997-12-11 (Box 61, Folder 13)
        - Rochester; Cornell Club of Rochester, 1998-01-10 (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - President's Circle Dinner-New York City, 1998-01-21 (Box 61, Folder 15)
        - Albany; (50th Anniversary of SUNY) and (Provost and senators), 1998-02-02 (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - Albany (State University Construction Fund), 1998-02-20 (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - Philadelphia Development and Columbus, Midland Board, 1998-02-21-1998-02-24 (Box 61, Folder 18)
        - Development (California and Northwest trip), 1998-03-02-1998-03-07 (Box 61, Folder 19)
        - Development (California and Northwest trip), 1998-03-02-1998-03-07 (Box 61, Folder 20)
        - Albany (bus trip); legislative reception, 1998-03-10 (Box 61, Folder 21)
        - Ithaca/Memphis (Personal), 1998-03-12-1998-03-15 (Box 61, Folder 22)
        - Zamorano, 1998-03-18-1998-03-22 (Box 61, Folder 23)
        - Vermont, 1998-04-05-1998-04-06 (Box 61, Folder 24)
        - Midland board meeting, 1998-04-21-1998-04-22 (Box 61, Folder 25)
        - Osceola and Washington, DC; Personal and Zamorano meeting, 1998-05-08-1998-05-11 (Box 61, Folder 26)
        - Albany, New York, 1998-05-13 (Box 61, Folder 27)
        - New York City-Tower Club dinner, 1998-05-14 (Box 61, Folder 28)
        - Commencement, 1998-05-22-1998-05-24 (Box 61, Folder 29)
        - Commencement, 1998-05-30 (Box 61, Folder 30)
        - Reunion, 1998-06-04-1998-06-07 (Box 61, Folder 31)
        - Zamorano, 1998-06-11-1998-06-14 (Box 61, Folder 32)
        - New York City, 1998-06-14 (Box 61, Folder 33)
        - New York City; Cornell Club, 1998-06-16-1998-06-17 (Box 61, Folder 34)
        - Atlanta (AAFCS meeting), 1998-06-26-1998-07-02 (Box 61, Folder 35)
        - Columbus, Ohio; Midland Board of Trustees, 1998-06-21-1998-06-22 (Box 61, Folder 36)
        - Arkansas (personal), 1998-07-29-1998-08-02 (Box 61, Folder 37)
        - Massachusetts; Francille Firebaugh's vacation, 1998-08-12-1998-08-17 (Box 61, Folder 38)
        - Human Ecology orientation, 1998-08-22 (Box 61, Folder 39)
        - Tuscon, Arizona (Personal), 1998-09-02-1998-09-07 (Box 61, Folder 40)
        - Washington, DC; Zamorano Development meeting, 1998-09-19-1998-09-21 (Box 61, Folder 41)
        - Human Ecology Advisory Council, 1998-09-25 (Box 61, Folder 42)
        - New York City and Arkansas, 1998-10-07-1998-10-12 (Box 61, Folder 43)
        - Homecoming, 1998-10-17 (Box 61, Folder 44)
        - Arkansas, 1998-10-29-1998-11-01 (Box 61, Folder 45)
        - Zamorano (Hondoras), 1998-11-04-1998-11-09 (Box 61, Folder 46)
        - New York City; Visit with James Tallon, 1998-11-16 (Box 61, Folder 47)
        - Chicago, 1998-11-18-1998-11-22 (Box 61, Folder 48)
        - Washington, D.C., 1998-12-03-1998-12-04 (Box 61, Folder 49)
        - Mini-conference of Family and Consumer Science Organization, 1998-12-05 (Box 61, Folder 50)
        - New York City; Families and Work, Alums, 1998-12-10-1998-12-11 (Box 61, Folder 51)
        - Sarasota, Florida; development, 1998-12-14-1998-12-18 (Box 61, Folder 52)
        - Arkansas and Rome (Francille Firebaugh and John Firebaugh), 1998-12-23 (Box 61, Folder 53)
        - Osceola, Arkansas, 1999-02-12-1999-02-14 (Box 61, Folder 54)
        - Columbus, Ohio (Midland) and Fort Meyers, Florida (development), 1999-02-23-1999-02-28 (Box 61, Folder 55)
        - Zamorano and Miami; Board meeting and development, 1999-03-03-1999-03-08 (Box 61, Folder 56)
        - Albany, New York; Legislative reception, 1999-3-09 (Box 61, Folder 57)
        - Albany, New York; Family Life Development Center dinner and meet with government officials, 1999-04-09-1999-04-10 (Box 61, Folder 58)
        - New York City - Human Ecology Advisory Council, Advancement Committee, Francille Firebaugh; Retirement reception and dinner, 1999-04-22-1999-04-25 (Box 61, Folder 59)
        - Columbus-Midland and Cleveland- Cayuga Society luncheon, 1999-04-27-1999-05-01 (Box 61, Folder 60)
        - New York City-Human Ecology Committee Chairs and Tower Club Dinner, 1999-05-14-1999-05-15 (Box 61, Folder 61)
      - c)Speeches Link to list of all the speech titles and dates given. PDF file.
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1988-10-05-1989-01-21 (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1989-01-30-1989-04-08 (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1989-04-09-1989-05-20 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1989-05-23-1989-08-26 (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1989-09-12-1989-10-20 (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1989-10-21-1990-04-05 (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1990-04-21-1990-06-26 (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1990-08-05-1990-10-11 (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1990-10-15-1990-11-15 (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1991-01-15-1991-04-17 (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1991-04-21-1991-06-08 (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1991-09-27-1991-11-21 (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1992-01-24-1992-03-26 (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1992-04-14-1992-06-17 (Box 42, Folder 15)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1992-06-19-1992-09-28 (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1992-10-02-1992-12-11 (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1993-01-15-1993-05-10 (Box 42, Folder 18)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1993-05-11-1993-09-12 (Box 42, Folder 19)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1992-09-13-1992-12-13 (Box 42, Folder 20)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1994-03-19-1994-06-18 (Box 42, Folder 21)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1994-08-08-1995-05-04 (Box 42, Folder 22)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1995-05-24-1995-12-15 (Box 42, Folder 23)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1996-02-07-1996-06-20 (Box 42, Folder 24)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1996-06-25-1996-10-10 (Box 42, Folder 25)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1996-10-21-1997-12-05 (Box 42, Folder 26)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1997-01-30-1997-06-06 (Box 42, Folder 27)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1997-06-06-1997-12-05 (Box 42, Folder 28)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1997-12-11-1998-04-29 (Box 42, Folder 29)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1998-04-28-1998-06-06 (Box 42, Folder 30)
        - Francille M. Firebaugh, Speeches, 1998-07-27-1998-12-18 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - 3) Subject Files and Correspondence (box 114 contains computer disks of correspondence (1980-1996)created in WordPerfect formatted for an IBM compatible computer)
      - Accessory Instruction, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Accessory Instruction, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Accounting:Salary Adjustments, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Accounting:Smith Lever Funding, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Admissions, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Advisory Council Minutes, etc., 1990, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Advisory Council- Membership Lists, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Advisory Council- Material concerning last 10 years of the College(1978-1988), Ziegler (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Advisory Council- Paper concerning the future of the College, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Affirmative Action Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Affirmative Action Committee, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Affirmative Action Committee, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Affirmative Action Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Alumni Affairs and Development Office, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Alumni Association- Long Range Goals, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Annual Reports- Dean's, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Annual Reports- Departments, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Annual Reports- Faculty Scholarly and Professional Activities, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Annual Reports- Consumer Economics and Housing- General, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Annual Reports- Alumni Association (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Annual Reports- Consumer Economics and Housing- General, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - College- Anniversary (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Master Plans, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Budget- Dean's Message and Planning Requests, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Budget, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Budget, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Budget - "Measures of Growth at Cornell", 1988 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Budget - Conferences, 1991-1993 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Calendars- Dean's, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Campaign Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Campaign Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Campaign- Capital, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Committee- Implementation Committee, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Certification- Home Economics- Faculty Meetings, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence- Dean's, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence- Dean's, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence- Dean's, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence concerning Research and Professional Programs, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Cooperative Extension Metropolitan Task Force, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Cooperative Extension Metropolitan Task Force, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Cooperative Extension- Associate Director/Human Ecology, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Cooperative Extension Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Commission on the Future of Cooperative Extension, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Cooperative Extension Program in New York City, 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Cooperative Extension Program in New York City, 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Cooperative Extension Advisory Council, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Cooperative Extension Budget, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Cooperative Extension Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Cooperative Extension Correspondence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Cooperative Extension- 4-H, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Cooperative Extension- 4-H, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Cooperative Extension- Broome County, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Cooperative Extension- Monroe County, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Cooperative Extension-New York City Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Cooperative Extension-New York City Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Cooperative Extension Metropolitan Working Group, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Cooperative Extension- Research, Land Grant Roles, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Cooperative Extension Staffing Needs, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Cooperative Extension Statewide Staffing Needs, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Enrollments, 1980-87 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Exchange Relationship- Javeriana University- Columbia, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Expanded Food and Nutritional Education Program (EFNEP), 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Family Life Development Center, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Field and International Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - General Foods (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Gerontology Program, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Gerontology- Courses, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Gerontology- Reports, Proposals, Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Gerontology- Establishment of Institute on Aging, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Gerontology- Faculty Interested (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Gerontology, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Gerontology, 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Goals of the College of Human Economics- Dean Canoyer, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Grievance Procedures, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - Hatch Act, 1985-1990 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Homes, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Household Time Use Conference- Attendance List and Dinner Speakers, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Household Time Use Conference- Program, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Program, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Session A, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Session B, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Session C, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Panel, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Household Time and Use Conference- Panel Discussion (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Human Ecology Council- Communication Plan, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Infant Project, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - International Activities, 1980-1992 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - International Program, including the Liberia Cornell Program, 1984, 1987, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - International Task Force- Survey, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - International Task Force, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Media Services, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Minority Students, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Migrant Program, 1982-1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Policy Concerning Part-time Students, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Procedure for Writing Bulletins, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Protestant Cooperative Ministry, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Public Affairs Program in the College - Assessment, 1988-06 (Box 13, Folder 8A)
      - Reorganization of the College, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Report- College Study on Undergraduate Education in Home Economics, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Report- "Committee to Develop Recruitment Marketing Strategies", 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Report- "A 1983 Look at a 1966 Document: A Review of the Final Report of the President's Committee to Study the College of Home Economics" (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Sloan Health Program- "Universal Access to Healthcare: A Fiscally Prudent Approach" by Roger Battistella (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Sloan Program- Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Sloan/Health Administration- Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Sloan Program- Report to the Provost, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Statutory Dean's Meetings, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Statutory Dean's Meeting, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Statutory Dean's Meeting, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Student Services Office, 1978-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Textiles and Apparel- Correspondence concerning Ph.D. Program, funding, etc., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Women- Association for Women in Development (AWID) Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Women in Development Material, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Women in Development (Publications), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Women in Development Seminar- Ohio State, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Undergraduate Education (Improving), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Undergraduate Education (Improving), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Commission on Undergraduate Education/ Common Learning, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Quantitative Literature (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - List of Nominees for the SUNY Chancellor's Award, 1977-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Associate Dean's Files- Refer to archival collection # 23/13/2365, Department of Human Development and Family Studies Records, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Enrollments, 1976-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)